<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tier VIII Tanks on Home</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/8/</link><description>Recent content in Tier VIII Tanks on Home</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/8/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tier VIII Light Tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/8/light-tanks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/8/light-tanks/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Premium Tank France FALSE AMX 13 90 France TRUE AMX Defender Germany TRUE leKpz M 41 90 mm Germany FALSE Spähpanzer Ru 251 UK FALSE FV301 USA FALSE T49 USSR TRUE LT-432 USSR FALSE T-54 ltwt.</description></item><item><title>Tier VIII Medium Tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/8/medium-tanks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/8/medium-tanks/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Premium Tank China TRUE 122 TM China TRUE 59-Patton China FALSE T-34-2 China TRUE T-34-3 China TRUE Type 59 European TRUE Lansen C European FALSE P.44 Pantera European TRUE Progetto M35 mod.</description></item><item><title>Tier VIII Heavy Tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/8/heavy-tanks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/8/heavy-tanks/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Premium Tank China TRUE 112 Glacial China FALSE WZ-110 China TRUE WZ-111 China TRUE WZ-112-2 European FALSE 53TP Markowskiego European TRUE EMIL 1951 European FALSE Emil I European TRUE Škoda T 56 France FALSE AMX 50 100 France TRUE AMX M4 mle.</description></item><item><title>Tier VIII Tank Destroyers</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/8/tank-destroyers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/8/tank-destroyers/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Premium Tank China FALSE WZ-111-1G FT China TRUE WZ-120-1G FT France FALSE AMX AC mle. 48 France TRUE AMX Canon d&amp;rsquo;assaut 105 Germany TRUE 8,8 cm Pak 43 Jagdtiger Germany FALSE Ferdinand Germany FALSE Jagdpanther II Germany TRUE Kanonenjagdpanzer 105 Germany TRUE Rheinmetall Skorpion G Germany FALSE Rhm.</description></item><item><title>Tier VIII Premium Tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/8/premium-tanks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/8/premium-tanks/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Vehicle Class Tank China Medium Tank 122 TM China Medium Tank 59-Patton China Medium Tank T-34-3 China Medium Tank Type 59 China Heavy Tank 112 Glacial China Heavy Tank WZ-111 China Heavy Tank WZ-112-2 China Tank Destroyer WZ-120-1G FT European Medium Tank Lansen C European Medium Tank Progetto M35 mod.</description></item><item><title>Tier VIII tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/8/tanks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/8/tanks/</guid><description>American Tanks Vehicle Class Premium Tank Light Tank FALSE T49 Medium Tank FALSE M26 Pershing Medium Tank TRUE T25 Pilot Number 1 Medium Tank TRUE T26E4 SuperPershing Medium Tank FALSE T69 Medium Tank TRUE T95E2 Heavy Tank TRUE Chrysler K Heavy Tank FALSE M-III-Yoh Heavy Tank TRUE M6A2E1 EXP Heavy Tank TRUE Scepter Heavy Tank TRUE T26E5 Heavy Tank FALSE T32 Heavy Tank TRUE T34 Heavy Tank TRUE T34 Independence Heavy Tank TRUE T54E2 Heavy Tank TRUE T77 Tank Destroyer FALSE T28 Tank Destroyer TRUE T28 Defender Tank Destroyer FALSE T28 Prototype Tank Destroyer TRUE TS-5 British Tanks Vehicle Class Premium Tank Light Tank FALSE FV301 Medium Tank TRUE Centurion Mk.</description></item><item><title>Tier VIII player stats</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/8/players/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/8/players/</guid><description>This page list statistics of players&amp;rsquo; battles at tier VIII during update 9.0.
Current WR vs. Career Battles played This graph shows players WR at the tier VIII during the update 9.</description></item></channel></rss>