<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tier VIII Tanks on Home</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.5/8/</link><description>Recent content in Tier VIII Tanks on Home</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.5/8/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tier VIII Light Tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.5/8/light-tanks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.5/8/light-tanks/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Premium Tank USSR TRUE LT-432 USSR FALSE T-54 ltwt. Germany TRUE HWK 30 Germany TRUE leKpz M 41 90 mm Germany FALSE Spähpanzer Ru 251 USA FALSE T49 USA TRUE T49 Fearless China FALSE WZ-132 France FALSE AMX 13 90 France TRUE AMX Defender UK TRUE FV1066 Senlac UK FALSE FV301 All the graphs are based on battles played during update 10.</description></item><item><title>Tier VIII Medium Tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.5/8/medium-tanks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.5/8/medium-tanks/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Premium Tank USSR TRUE Object 274a USSR TRUE ST-62 Version 2 USSR TRUE STG USSR FALSE T-44 USSR TRUE T-44-100 USSR TRUE T-54 first prototype Germany FALSE Indien-Panzer Germany TRUE Kampfpanzer 07 RH Germany TRUE Kpz.</description></item><item><title>Tier VIII Heavy Tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.5/8/heavy-tanks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.5/8/heavy-tanks/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Premium Tank USSR TRUE IS-2Sh USSR FALSE IS-3 USSR TRUE IS-3 Defender USSR TRUE IS-5 (Object 730) USSR TRUE IS-6 USSR TRUE IS-6 Fearless USSR FALSE KV-4 USSR TRUE KV-5 USSR TRUE Object 252U USSR TRUE T-2020 Germany TRUE E 75 TS Germany TRUE Keiler Germany TRUE Löwe Germany FALSE Tiger II Germany FALSE VK 100.</description></item><item><title>Tier VIII Tank Destroyers</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.5/8/tank-destroyers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.5/8/tank-destroyers/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Premium Tank USSR TRUE ISU-130 USSR FALSE ISU-152 USSR FALSE SU-101 USSR TRUE SU-130PM Germany TRUE 8,8 cm Pak 43 Jagdtiger Germany FALSE Ferdinand Germany FALSE Jagdpanther II Germany TRUE Kanonenjagdpanzer 105 Germany TRUE Rheinmetall Skorpion G Germany FALSE Rhm.</description></item><item><title>Tier VIII Premium Tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.5/8/premium-tanks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.5/8/premium-tanks/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Vehicle Class Tank USSR Light Tank LT-432 USSR Medium Tank Object 274a USSR Medium Tank ST-62 Version 2 USSR Medium Tank STG USSR Medium Tank T-44-100 USSR Medium Tank T-54 first prototype USSR Heavy Tank IS-2Sh USSR Heavy Tank IS-3 Defender USSR Heavy Tank IS-5 (Object 730) USSR Heavy Tank IS-6 USSR Heavy Tank IS-6 Fearless USSR Heavy Tank KV-5 USSR Heavy Tank Object 252U USSR Heavy Tank T-2020 USSR Tank Destroyer ISU-130 USSR Tank Destroyer SU-130PM Germany Light Tank HWK 30 Germany Light Tank leKpz M 41 90 mm Germany Medium Tank Kampfpanzer 07 RH Germany Medium Tank Kpz.</description></item><item><title>Tier VIII tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.5/8/tanks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.5/8/tanks/</guid><description>American Tanks Vehicle Class Premium Tank Light Tank FALSE T49 Light Tank TRUE T49 Fearless Medium Tank TRUE ASTRON Rex 105 mm Medium Tank FALSE M26 Pershing Medium Tank TRUE T25 Pilot Number 1 Medium Tank TRUE T26E4 SuperPershing Medium Tank FALSE T69 Medium Tank TRUE T95E2 Heavy Tank TRUE Chrysler K Heavy Tank FALSE M-III-Yoh Heavy Tank TRUE M-IV-Y Heavy Tank TRUE M6A2E1 EXP Heavy Tank TRUE Scepter Heavy Tank TRUE T26E5 Heavy Tank FALSE T32 Heavy Tank TRUE T34 Heavy Tank TRUE T34 Independence Heavy Tank TRUE T54E2 Heavy Tank TRUE T77 Tank Destroyer FALSE T28 Tank Destroyer TRUE T28 Defender Tank Destroyer FALSE T28 Prototype Tank Destroyer TRUE TS-5 Tank Destroyer TRUE TS-60 British Tanks Vehicle Class Premium Tank Light Tank TRUE FV1066 Senlac Light Tank FALSE FV301 Medium Tank TRUE Centurion Mk.</description></item><item><title>Tier VIII player stats</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.5/8/players/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.5/8/players/</guid><description>This page list statistics of players&amp;rsquo; battles at tier VIII during update 10.5.
Current WR vs. Career Battles played This graph shows players WR at the tier VIII during the update 10.</description></item></channel></rss>