<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>7.6 - Tag - Home</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/tags/7.6/</link><description/><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blitzanalysiz.com/tags/7.6/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>1 Million players</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/blog/2021-02-27_1m_accounts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/blog/2021-02-27_1m_accounts/</guid><description>BlitzAnalysiz[] recently reach an impressive milestone: the site’s database tracks now over 1 million players! That’s is a big number so let’s have a look on the player base.
Career WR The chart below shows player’s career WR over those 1M players. The career WR distribution seems almost normal distribution, but only almost. The right-hand side “tail” is reaching further from the mean vs. the left-hand side and the mean WR is above 50%. This seems impossible. This is likely related to the sampling of the players, since more active players are more likely to end up in the the database. Many players (38%) have given up the game or at least have not played in 2021. It seems the the success of the player does not influence on the decision to give up on the game - at least among those who have ended into the database.</description></item><item><title>Update 7.6 final stats added</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/blog/2021-02-27_7.6_final_stats_added/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/blog/2021-02-27_7.6_final_stats_added/</guid><description>Final stats for update 7.6 have been added.
update 7.6 marked a great milestone for the site. BlitzAnalysiz[] is now tracking the performance of more than 1 million players!
In total, there were 328M battles by 515k players recorded in the database during the update 7.6.</description></item><item><title>Vehicle Class (Im)Balance</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/blog/2021-03-13_vehicle_class_imbalance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/blog/2021-03-13_vehicle_class_imbalance/</guid><description>I my view, the game became more boring after WG added Vehicle Class Matching rules into the MatchMaker (update 5.1). The exact vehicle class matching rules have been adjusted since, but basically the Vehicle Class Matching limits the number of Tank Destroyers and Light Tanks per team and makes sure there is only +/-1 tank difference between the teams across the vehicle classes. This results mirrored teams causing monotonic battles. In my view, most of the vehicle class matching rules should be abolished, but I know well how I am in the minority here.</description></item></channel></rss>