<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Players on Home</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/tags/players/</link><description>Recent content in Players on Home</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blitzanalysiz.com/tags/players/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Players</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.2/players/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.2/players/</guid><description>Battles per Player The graph shows the number of battles fought per player during the update 11.2. On average, players played 138 battles and the median battle count was 32. The following tables shows battle counts by N% most inactive players during the update.</description></item><item><title>Players</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.1/players/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.1/players/</guid><description>Battles per Player The graph shows the number of battles fought per player during the update 11.1. On average, players played 855 battles and the median battle count was 65. The following tables shows battle counts by N% most inactive players during the update.</description></item><item><title>Players</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.0/players/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.0/players/</guid><description>Battles per Player The graph shows the number of battles fought per player during the update 11.0. On average, players played 104 battles and the median battle count was 26. The following tables shows battle counts by N% most inactive players during the update.</description></item><item><title>Players</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.8/players/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.8/players/</guid><description>Battles per Player The graph shows the number of battles fought per player during the update 10.8. On average, players played 123 battles and the median battle count was 30. The following tables shows battle counts by N% most inactive players during the update.</description></item><item><title>Players</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.7/players/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.7/players/</guid><description>Battles per Player The graph shows the number of battles fought per player during the update 10.7. On average, players played 142 battles and the median battle count was 30. The following tables shows battle counts by N% most inactive players during the update.</description></item><item><title>Players</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.6/players/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.6/players/</guid><description>Battles per Player The graph shows the number of battles fought per player during the update 10.6. On average, players played 138 battles and the median battle count was 31. The following tables shows battle counts by N% most inactive players during the update.</description></item><item><title>Players</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.5/players/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.5/players/</guid><description>Battles per Player The graph shows the number of battles fought per player during the update 10.5. On average, players played 130 battles and the median battle count was 31. The following tables shows battle counts by N% most inactive players during the update.</description></item><item><title>Players</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.4/players/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.4/players/</guid><description>Battles per Player The graph shows the number of battles fought per player during the update 10.4. On average, players played 117 battles and the median battle count was 26. The following tables shows battle counts by N% most inactive players during the update.</description></item><item><title>Players</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.3/players/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.3/players/</guid><description>Battles per Player The graph shows the number of battles fought per player during the update 10.3. On average, players played 152 battles and the median battle count was 34. The following tables shows battle counts by N% most inactive players during the update.</description></item><item><title>Players</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.2/players/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.2/players/</guid><description>Battles per Player The graph shows the number of battles fought per player during the update 10.2. On average, players played 131 battles and the median battle count was 31. The following tables shows battle counts by N% most inactive players during the update.</description></item><item><title>Players</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.0/players/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.0/players/</guid><description>Battles per Player The graph shows the number of battles fought per player during the update 10.0. On average, players played 127 battles and the median battle count was 29. The following tables shows battle counts by N% most inactive players during the update.</description></item><item><title>Players</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.1/players/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.1/players/</guid><description>Battles per Player The graph shows the number of battles fought per player during the update 10.1. On average, players played 123 battles and the median battle count was 32. The following tables shows battle counts by N% most inactive players during the update.</description></item></channel></rss>