<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tier IX Tanks on Home</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.4/9/</link><description>Recent content in Tier IX Tanks on Home</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.4/9/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tier IX Light Tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.4/9/light-tanks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.4/9/light-tanks/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Premium Tank USSR FALSE Object 84 USA FALSE T92E1 China FALSE WZ-132A France FALSE Bat.-Châtillon 25 t AP UK FALSE Vickers Cruiser All the graphs are based on battles played during update 10.</description></item><item><title>Tier IX Medium Tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.4/9/medium-tanks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.4/9/medium-tanks/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Premium Tank USSR FALSE T-54 Germany FALSE E 50 Germany FALSE Leopard Prototyp A USA FALSE M46 Patton USA FALSE T54E1 China FALSE WZ-120 France TRUE AMX 30 1er prototype France TRUE Char Futur 4 UK FALSE Centurion Mk.</description></item><item><title>Tier IX Heavy Tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.4/9/heavy-tanks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.4/9/heavy-tanks/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Premium Tank USSR FALSE IS-8 USSR TRUE K-91 USSR TRUE Object 452K USSR TRUE Object 752 USSR FALSE ST-I Germany FALSE E 75 Germany TRUE Kampfpanzer 70 Germany FALSE Mäuschen Germany FALSE VK 45.</description></item><item><title>Tier IX Tank Destroyers</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.4/9/tank-destroyers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.4/9/tank-destroyers/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Premium Tank USSR FALSE Object 704 USSR FALSE SU-122-54 Germany FALSE Jagdtiger Germany FALSE Waffenträger auf Pz. IV Germany TRUE Waffenträger Ritter USA FALSE T30 USA FALSE T95 China FALSE WZ-111G FT France FALSE AMX 50 Foch UK FALSE FV4004 Conway UK FALSE Tortoise Japan FALSE Ho-Ri Type II Europe FALSE Controcarro 1 Mk.</description></item><item><title>Tier IX Premium Tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.4/9/premium-tanks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.4/9/premium-tanks/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Vehicle Class Tank USSR Heavy Tank K-91 USSR Heavy Tank Object 452K USSR Heavy Tank Object 752 Germany Heavy Tank Kampfpanzer 70 Germany Tank Destroyer Waffenträger Ritter USA Heavy Tank AE Phase I USA Heavy Tank TL-7-120 China Heavy Tank BZ-58-2 China Heavy Tank WZ-114 France Medium Tank AMX 30 1er prototype France Medium Tank Char Futur 4 UK Medium Tank Cobra Other Medium Tank Glacier Other Medium Tank T 55A Other Heavy Tank Regressor Europe Heavy Tank 50TP prototyp All the graphs are based on battles played during update 10.</description></item><item><title>Tier IX tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.4/9/tanks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.4/9/tanks/</guid><description>American Tanks Vehicle Class Premium Tank Light Tank FALSE T92E1 Medium Tank FALSE M46 Patton Medium Tank FALSE T54E1 Heavy Tank TRUE AE Phase I Heavy Tank FALSE M-V-Yoh Heavy Tank FALSE M103 Heavy Tank TRUE TL-7-120 Tank Destroyer FALSE T30 Tank Destroyer FALSE T95 British Tanks Vehicle Class Premium Tank Light Tank FALSE Vickers Cruiser Medium Tank FALSE Centurion Mk.</description></item><item><title>Tier IX player stats</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.4/9/players/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/10.4/9/players/</guid><description>This page list statistics of players&amp;rsquo; battles at tier IX during update 10.4.
Current WR vs. Career Battles played This graph shows players WR at the tier IX during the update 10.</description></item></channel></rss>