<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tier VI Tanks on Home</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/6/</link><description>Recent content in Tier VI Tanks on Home</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/6/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tier VI Light Tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/6/light-tanks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/6/light-tanks/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Premium Tank China TRUE Type 64 France FALSE AMX 12 t France TRUE AMXmas Germany TRUE Agent Germany FALSE VK 28.01 USA FALSE M24 Chaffee USA TRUE Ranger USA TRUE T21 USA FALSE T37 USSR FALSE MT-25 Other TRUE Titan T24 57 All the graphs are based on battles played during update 9.</description></item><item><title>Tier VI Medium Tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/6/medium-tanks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/6/medium-tanks/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Premium Tank China TRUE Ox China FALSE Type 58 European TRUE Blaze European FALSE P.43 bis European TRUE P.43/06 anniversario European TRUE Pudel European FALSE Škoda T 25 European FALSE Strv 74 European TRUE Turbo France TRUE Bretagne Panther Germany TRUE Pz.</description></item><item><title>Tier VI Heavy Tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/6/heavy-tanks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/6/heavy-tanks/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Premium Tank European FALSE 40TP Habicha France FALSE ARL 44 France TRUE Eraser BP44 Germany TRUE Barkhan Germany TRUE Icebreaker Germany TRUE Tiger 131 Germany FALSE VK 36.</description></item><item><title>Tier VI Tank Destroyers</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/6/tank-destroyers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/6/tank-destroyers/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Premium Tank China FALSE WZ-131G FT France FALSE ARL V39 France TRUE Charles Germany TRUE Dicker Max Germany FALSE Jagdpanzer IV Germany TRUE Kryos Germany FALSE Nashorn UK FALSE AT 8 UK TRUE Churchill Gun Carrier UK TRUE Dreadnought USA FALSE M18 Hellcat USA FALSE M36 Jackson USSR FALSE SU-100 USSR TRUE SU-100Y All the graphs are based on battles played during update 9.</description></item><item><title>Tier VI Premium Tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/6/premium-tanks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/6/premium-tanks/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Vehicle Class Tank China Light Tank Type 64 China Medium Tank Ox European Medium Tank Blaze European Medium Tank P.43/06 anniversario European Medium Tank Pudel European Medium Tank Turbo France Light Tank AMXmas France Medium Tank Bretagne Panther France Heavy Tank Eraser BP44 France Tank Destroyer Charles Germany Light Tank Agent Germany Medium Tank Pz.</description></item><item><title>Tier VI tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/6/tanks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/6/tanks/</guid><description>American Tanks Vehicle Class Premium Tank Light Tank FALSE M24 Chaffee Light Tank TRUE Ranger Light Tank TRUE T21 Light Tank FALSE T37 Medium Tank TRUE BLTZ9000 Medium Tank TRUE M4A3E2 Sherman Jumbo Medium Tank TRUE M4A3E8 Fury Medium Tank FALSE M4A3E8 Sherman Medium Tank TRUE Rudolph Heavy Tank FALSE M6 Heavy Tank TRUE Magnus Tank Destroyer FALSE M18 Hellcat Tank Destroyer FALSE M36 Jackson British Tanks Vehicle Class Premium Tank Medium Tank TRUE AC IV Sentinel Medium Tank FALSE Cromwell Medium Tank TRUE Cromwell B Medium Tank TRUE Explorer Medium Tank FALSE Sherman Firefly Heavy Tank TRUE Blasteroid Heavy Tank TRUE Churchill Mk.</description></item><item><title>Tier VI player stats</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/6/players/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/6/players/</guid><description>This page list statistics of players&amp;rsquo; battles at tier VI during update 9.0.
Current WR vs. Career Battles played This graph shows players WR at the tier VI during the update 9.</description></item></channel></rss>