<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tier X Tanks on Home</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.0/10/</link><description>Recent content in Tier X Tanks on Home</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.0/10/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tier X Light Tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.0/10/light-tanks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.0/10/light-tanks/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Premium Tank USSR FALSE T-100 LT USA FALSE XM551 Sheridan China FALSE WZ-132-1 France FALSE Bat.-Châtillon 25 t UK FALSE Vickers Light 105 All the graphs are based on battles played during update 11.</description></item><item><title>Tier X Medium Tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.0/10/medium-tanks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.0/10/medium-tanks/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Premium Tank USSR FALSE Object 140 USSR TRUE Object 907 USSR TRUE T-22 medium USSR FALSE T-62A Germany FALSE E 50 Ausf. M Germany TRUE Kampfpanzer 50 t Germany FALSE Leopard 1 USA FALSE M48 Patton USA TRUE M60 China TRUE 121B China FALSE WZ-121 France TRUE AMX 30 B UK FALSE FV4202 Japan FALSE STB-1 Europe TRUE Carro da Combattimento 45t Europe FALSE CS-63 Europe FALSE Progetto M40 mod.</description></item><item><title>Tier X Heavy Tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.0/10/heavy-tanks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.0/10/heavy-tanks/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Premium Tank USSR FALSE IS-4 USSR FALSE IS-7 USSR TRUE Object 260 USSR TRUE Object 777 Version II Germany FALSE E 100 Germany FALSE Maus Germany FALSE VK 72.</description></item><item><title>Tier X Tank Destroyers</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.0/10/tank-destroyers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.0/10/tank-destroyers/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Premium Tank USSR FALSE Object 263 USSR FALSE Object 268 USSR TRUE Object 268 Version 4 Germany FALSE Grille 15 Germany FALSE Jagdpanzer E 100 USA FALSE T110E3 USA FALSE T110E4 USA TRUE XM66F China FALSE WZ-113G FT France FALSE AMX 50 Foch (155) UK FALSE FV215b (183) UK TRUE FV217 Badger UK FALSE FV4005 Japan FALSE Ho-Ri Type III Europe FALSE Controcarro 3 Minotauro All the graphs are based on battles played during update 11.</description></item><item><title>Tier X Premium Tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.0/10/premium-tanks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.0/10/premium-tanks/</guid><description>Show Tanks Nation Vehicle Class Tank USSR Medium Tank Object 907 USSR Medium Tank T-22 medium USSR Heavy Tank Object 260 USSR Heavy Tank Object 777 Version II USSR Tank Destroyer Object 268 Version 4 Germany Medium Tank Kampfpanzer 50 t Germany Heavy Tank VK 90.</description></item><item><title>Tier X tanks</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.0/10/tanks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.0/10/tanks/</guid><description>American Tanks Vehicle Class Premium Tank Light Tank FALSE XM551 Sheridan Medium Tank FALSE M48 Patton Medium Tank TRUE M60 Heavy Tank TRUE Concept 1B Heavy Tank FALSE M-VI-Yoh Heavy Tank FALSE T110E5 Heavy Tank FALSE T57 Heavy Tank Heavy Tank TRUE T95E6 Tank Destroyer FALSE T110E3 Tank Destroyer FALSE T110E4 Tank Destroyer TRUE XM66F British Tanks Vehicle Class Premium Tank Light Tank FALSE Vickers Light 105 Medium Tank FALSE FV4202 Heavy Tank TRUE Chieftain Mk.</description></item><item><title>Tier X player stats</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.0/10/players/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/11.0/10/players/</guid><description>This page list statistics of players&amp;rsquo; battles at tier X during update 11.0.
Current WR vs. Career Battles played This graph shows players WR at the tier X during the update 11.</description></item></channel></rss>